

Väinö Kasurinen

Computer science student

Github: VKasurinen

Contact:



LinkedIn



vaino.kasurinen@hotmail.fi



0449750078

Skills

- Java Advanced
- · Python Good
- SQL (MySql) Basics
- HTML & CSS Good
- · React.js Good
- · Kotlin Good
- · Git Advanced
- · Problem solving-Advanced
- · Teamworking Advanced

Language

Finnish ••••

English • • •

Swedish • •

Interests

- · Sports- Crossfit, Football
- Programming
- Mobile and Web development

About me

Hi, I'm a 20-year-old computer science student. After upper secondary school, I was interested in making software and coding in general, and because of this, I am now studying computer science for the second year. By nature, I am determined, calm and confident. I like to work in teams, and I am very motivated to try my skills on the software development side. I'm not afraid to work under pressure, and if I need to learn something I've usually learned it and completed the required task. So, I am guick learner and open to new information.

Education

University of Oulu, Computer science 09/2022-

University of Eastern Finland, Computer science

09/2021 - 05/2022 Open university studies

Siilinjärven lukio, Matriculation examination 08/2018 - 06/2021

Work experience

Sakupe Oy, Textile caretaker 6/2019, 6/2020, 3/2021 - 8/2021, 5/2022 - 8/2022

My work included:

- -Making orders for clients
- -Wash different textiles